so Apple number 60 is I want to call it
crowd source production so anything
that's intangible good
mainly electronics I would say but even
things like eyeglasses or I mean
anything you can think of it we buy we
can come up with a better version that's
cheaper more durable with crowd sourcing
so we can design it together we can make
it in bulk and I think I believe would
just be a better product because you're
not in competition with everyone else if
you have a million people that say I
will absolutely buy a car if it's
$10,000 and state-of-the-art and
everything then it can be done for that
and here I'm able to upgrade it
constantly and I'll have to get a new
one ever and it's electric and a nozzle
of features and I mean then you have ten
mil a billion people who are going to
build by a $10,000 car and you don't
need to starting a car company would be
next to impossible
that's your Tesla but creating a car in
this system would be very easy because
you already have the user base like if
Google came up with a car it made sense
it would be a lot easier for them to get
into the auto industry then random Joe
Schmo right so a crowdsource production
mortgage is like with every other the
technological ideas that I have for you
a space where you can go online and
discuss problems and solutions and the
solutions being a technological app or
website it's the same but for actual
tangible goods
so Apple number 60 is crowd-sourced
production